ILGWU Related Sound Recordings 6036/073 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Related Sound Recordings
1935-1966
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU)
6036/073 AV
2.33 cubic feet
2.3 linear ft.
Sound recordings.
The collection consists of sound recordings, primarily LPs and 78s. These recordings were either created, produced, or utilized by the ILGWU for radio, conventions, or performances, or contain material and songs with a labor and union focus.
7528178
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 17, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of an assortment of sound recordings in various formats, mainly LPs and 78s. Much of the recordings are ILGWU produced, either songs, speeches, or broadcasts. Of particular note are the recordings of "Pins and Needles, " the ILGWU broadway musical revue from 1937. There are recordings of the original cast, as well as the 25th Anniversary Edition of "Pins and Needles" with Barbara Striesand. Also interesting are the recordings of various union choirs and productions from locals and departments. Included in the collection are LPs of performers and songs that have a labor and union focus. Another component is the sound recordings of speeches and presentations, by ILGWU president David Dubinsky and other union leaders as well as U.S. presidents and politicians. These are in the forms of interviews, proceedings at conventions, and events and anniversaries of locals. There are numerous recordings of radio broadcasts, identified by the various stations, many of which are Luigi Antonini radio addresses and the "Voice of 89."
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780 AV: ILGWU Audio-Visual (AV)
Pins and Needles.; Antonini, Luigi.; Dubinsky, David.; Kennedy, John.; Johnson, Lyndon.; Richardson, Herb.; Streisand, Barbara.; Truman, Harry.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.
7528178
- Two/Two for the Union, 1962-1965; 1 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Two Presidents of the United States and two garment workers talk about the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union and unionism. Side 1 includes President Lyndon Johnson when he came to New York City on June 6, 1964 to participate in the 50th anniversary celebration of the Union Health Center and President John Kennedy on May 19, 1962 at the ceremony to dedicate the ILGWU Cooperative Houses. Side 2 includes Pauline Newman and Judy Ackerman speaking at the 32nd Convention of the ILGWU in Miami Beach. Newman addressed the delegates on May 13, 1965 and Ackerman spoke on May 20, 1965.
- Two/Two for the Union, 1962-1965; 2 (Box 1)
- Two/Two for the Union, 1962-1965; 3 (Box 1)
- The Northeast Sings, 1965; 4 (Box 1)
  Members from the Northeast Department perform original songs at the 32nd ILGWU Convention in Miami Beach on May 17, 1965. Side A includes "ILGWU Anthem," "The Northeast," "Little Machine," "Join With Us," "This is a Strike," "They Can't Win," "Mr. Boss," "There Has Come a New Day," "It's So Different," and "With a Union, Grow, Grow." Side B includes "Learn to Love," "You Gotta Know the Score," Union Label," "It's A Grand Feeling," "So Long, Jenny," "Finale."
- The Northeast Sings, 1965; 5 (Box 1)
- The Northeast Sings, 1965; 6 (Box 1)
- Herb Richardson Sings of Labor, Hope and Freedom, 7 (Box 1)
  From the Labor Alumni Association of Rutgers University. Contents include: "Suzanne," "Which Side are You On," "Danny Boy," "Roll the Union On," "Take this Hammer," "It Could be a Wonderful World," "Oh Freedom," "We Shall Overcome," "So Big and Wonderful," "No Man is an Island," "We Shall not be Moved," "The Mill was Made of Marble," "If I Had a Hammer," "Solidarity Forever."
- Herb Richardson Sings of Labor, Hope and Freedom, 8 (Box 1)
- Strike! The Lawrence, Massachusetts Textile Strike of 1912, 9 (Box 1)
  Side 1: Life in Lawrence, The "Foreigners," The Strike Begins, Events During the Strike; Side 2: Events During the Strike, The Trial of Ettor and Giovannitti, Perspectives on the Past, The Women's Strike of 1909, a firsthand account by Pauline M. Newman
- Joe Glazer and the PAC Bucks, 10 (Box 1)
  "Solidarity" and "Give Away Boys"
- The Voice of Local 89 Broadcast on March 16, 1935, 11 (Box 1)
  Luigi Antonini
- The Voice of Local 89 Broadcast on March 16, 1935, 12 (Box 1)
- The Voice of Local 89 Broadcast on March 16, 1935, 13 (Box 1)
- KFMV "Lippy Duckatt-Sports Aud. For KF", 14 (Box 1)
- "Dramatic Sketch" from WEVD on 9/30/51 at 1:30 pm part 3 and 6, 1951; 15 (Box 1)
- "Dramatic Sketch" from WEVD on 9/30/51 at 1:30 pm part 2 and 5, 1951; 16 (Box 1)
- "Dramatic Sketch" from WEVD on 9/30/51 at 1:30 pm part 1 and 4, 1951; 17 (Box 1)
- ORT Mr. Dubinsky at the Commodore Hotel 1/31/43, 1943; 18 (Box 1)
- Prime Minister of Italy October 11, 1944, 19 (Box 1)
  Premier Ivanoe speech for Columbus Day October 12, 1944
- Luigi Antonini Address from WEVD on June 29, 1957, 20 (Box 1)
  Luigi Antonini Address; WEVD; June 29, 1957; 10:00 AM; Time-- 11:35
- Luigi Antonini Address from WEVD on June 15, 1957, 21 (Box 1)
  Luigi Antonini Address; WEVD; June 15, 1957; Time--13:27
- Luigi Antonini from Rome on Sept. 20, 1946 part 2, 22 (Box 1)
  Luigi Antonini From Rome (CT); Part Two #13525; Sept. 20, 1946
- Luigi Antonini from Rome on Sept. 20, 1946 part 1, 23 (Box 1)
  Luigi Antonini From Rome (CT); Part One #13525; Septe. 20, 1946
- Luigi Antonini on September 27, 1946 part 2, 24 (Box 1)
  Luigi Antonini, Part Two 13525, September 27, 1946
- Voice of Local 89 with Giovanni Canini on April 19th, 1952, 25 (Box 1)
  Voice of Local 89. Guest Speaker: Hon. Giovanni Canini Vice Secr. C.I.S.L. Radio Program April 19th, 1952 (as per V. Montana). Time 5:24. 3/20/1952
- Voice of Local 89 with Enrico Parri on April 5th, 1952, 26 (Box 1)
  Guest Speaker: On. Enrico Parri. April 5th, 1952 Radio Program. Enrico Parri Vice Secr. C.I.S.L. Time 4:33. 3/20/52.
- Voice of Local 89 with Mario Longhena on March 22nd, 1952, 27 (Box 1)
  "Voice of Local '89". Guest Speaker: Hon. Mario Longhena President Italian Red Cross. March 22nd, 1952 Radio Program. Time 3:00. 3/20/52.
- Voice of Local 89 with Giulio Pastore on March 29th, 1952, 28 (Box 1)
  "Voice of Local 89" Radio Program. March 29th, 1952. Guest Speaker: On. Giulio Pastore, Gen. Secr. C.I.S.L. Time 5:41. 3/20/52
- Untitled, 29 (Box 1)
- Untitled, 30 (Box 1)
- Sardis - Sam Levene on 8-26-49 part 1, 1949; 31 (Box 1)
  SARDIS - Sam Levene. 8-26-49. Part One. Serial 19320.
- I.L.G.W.U. David Dubinsky and I.L.G.W.U. Movie, 1949; 32 (Box 1)
  I.L.G.W.U. David Dubinsky and I.L.G.W.U. Movie. SARDIS - Sam Levene. 8-26- 49. Serial 19320. Part Two.
- Geneva Rebroadcast with David Dubinsky on 4/12/35 part 1 and 3, 1935; 33 (Box 1)
  Geneva Rebroadcast with David Dubinsky on station W.J.Z. on 4/12/35.
- Geneva Rebroadcast with David Dubinsky on 4/12/35 part 2 and 4, 1935; 34 (Box 1)
  Geneva Rebroadcast with David Dubinsky on 4/12/35. Station W.J.Z.
- 10.00-10.15 on 11-21-35 part 1 and 3, 1935; 35 (Box 1)
  Station W.B.N.X.
- 10.00-10.15 on 11-21-1935 part 2 and 4, 36 (Box 1)
- 10.00-10.30 P.M. on 10/10/35 part 6 and 8, 1935; 37 (Box 1)
  Station W.B.N.X
- David Dubinsky on Recreational Activities for Workers part 1 and 3, 1938; 38 (Box 1)
  David Dubinsky on Recreational Activities for Workers. Station W.J.Z. Date 4/14/38
- David Dubinsky on Recreational Activities for Workers on 4/14/38 part 2 and 4, 1938; 39 (Box 1)
  David Dubinsky on Recreational Activates for Workers on 4/14/38 part 2 and 4. Station W.J.Z.
- Union Convention on 5/27/40 with David Dubinsky part 1 and 3, 1940; 40 (Box 1)
  "union Convention" with David Dubinsky of "International Ladies Garment Workers" from Station W.E.V.D. on 5/27/40.
- Union Convention with David Dubinsky on 5/27/40 part 2 and 4, 1940; 41 (Box 1)
  "Union Convention" with David Dubinsky of "International Ladies Garment Workers" from Station W.E.V.D. on 5/27/40.
- Untitled, 42 (Box 1)
- Union Convention with David Dubinsky on 5/27/40 part 9 and 11, 1940; 43 (Box 1)
  "Union Convention" with David Dubinsky of "International Ladies Garment Workers" from Station W.E.V.D. on 5/27/40
- Union Convention with David Dubinsky on 5/27/40 part 10 and 12, 1940; 44 (Box 1)
- Int. Ladies Garment Workers Interviews with Taft Hartley Song and Gregory Peck on 10/28/48, 1948; 45 (Box 1)
  Int. Ladies Garment Workers Interviews with Taft Hartley Song and Gregory Peck. ABC #56. 10/28/48.
- Int. Ladies Garment Workers Interviews with Gene Kelly and Taft Hartley Song on 10/28/48, 1948; 46 (Box 1)
  Int. Ladies Garment Workers Interviews with Gene Kelly and Taft Hartley Song on 10/28/48. ABC #56
- "Fight for Civil Rights" on 11/1/60, 1960; 47 (Box 1)
  Gotham Recording Corporation. 1. Mrs. Roosevelt 6:33 2. Sen. Morse 6:17 3. Hon. H. Lehman 6:00
- The Truth About Civil Rights, 48 (Box 1)
  For ILGWU Campaign Committee. Broadcasts 11/1, 2, 3, 5. Side A: Band 1 - Governor Adlai E. Stevenson. Band 2 - Sen. Herbert H. Lehman, U.S. Senator, New York. Side B: Band 1 - Senator Paul H. Douglas, U.S. Senator, Illinois. Band 2 - Mrs. Eleanor Roosevelt. Presented by Committee on Political Education (COPE - AFL-CIO) Washington D.C.
- Democratic National Committee with Sammy Davis Jr., 49 (Box 1)
  Sammy Davis Jr. sings "How About You"
- George Meany, Sec'y-Treas., A.F.L., 50 (Box 1)
  Cuts #1 and #2 - same
- Registration Spots being used as Public Service in Connecticut, 51 (Box 1)
  From: Al Hamilton
- Dubinsky on 6/13/37, 1937; 52 (Box 1)
  Dubinsky #6. Station WEVD. Date 6/13/37/. Time 10:30.
- Speech made by Mr. David Dubinsky in Rome, Italy, 1948; 53 (Box 1)
  From Palermo. July 24, 1948. 10 A.M.
- Address by David Dubinsky on 07/24/48, 1948; 54 (Box 1)
  Broadcast by short wave from Italy (Palermo) July 24, 1948.
- 10/28/52, 1952; 55 (Box 1)
  Side 1: Humphrey Bogart, 5"10', Bill Mauldin, Herman Wouk. Side 2: Herman Wouk with Jingle, Richard Rogers, Agnes DeMille, Letter from Korea, John Gunther. 10/28/52
- ORT Mr. Dubinsky, 56 (Box 1)
- Mr. David Dubinsky on 11-1-42, 1942; 57 (Box 1)
  Mr. David Dubinsky from W.E.V.D.
- Eternal Light of 6/29 on July 10, 1958, 58 (Box 1)
  Eternal Light of 6/29 Side 1 and 2
- Eternal Light of 6/29 on July 10, 1958, 59 (Box 1)
  Eternal Light of 6/29 Side 1 and 2. This was a play on the Eternal Light radio program on DD.
- "Merrily we Roll Along" by Stevenson on 10/27/52, 1952; 60 (Box 1)
  2 identical cuts. 10/27/52.
- Umbay on 11-18-54 part 1, 1954; 61 (Box 1)
  Side 1. CT4176.
- Umbay on 11-18-54 part 2, 1954; 62 (Box 1)
  Side 2
- Inaugural of Seamen's House in London with Mr. David Dubinsky on 7/23/42 part 5, 1942; 63 (Box 1)
  Inaugural of Seamen's House in London with Mr. David Dubinsky on 7/23/42. 5.
- Inaugural of Seamen's House in London with Mr. David Dubinsky on 7/23/42 part 2, 1942; 64 (Box 1)
  Inaugural of Seamen's House in London with Mr. David Dubinsky on 7/23/42. 2.
- Opening Ceremonies of Seamen's Club in England with Mr. Dubinsky on 7/23/42 part 5, 1942; 65 (Box 1)
  Opening Ceremonies of Seamen's Club in England with Mr. Dubinsky. 5.
- Opening Ceremonies of Seamen's Club in England on 7/23/42 part 2, 1942; 66 (Box 1)
  Opening Ceremonies of Seamen's Club in England on 7/23/42. 2.
- Opening Ceremonies of Seamen's Club in England on 7/23/42 part 4, 1942; 67 (Box 1)
  Opening Ceremonies of Seamen's Club in England on 7/23/42. 4.
- Sammy Davis Jr. Get-Out-The-Vote Spots on 10/26/56, 1956; 1 (Box 2)
  Cut 1 - 1:00. Cut 2 - 0:20.
- "Canciones de la Huelga" (Songs of the Strike) by Luis Valdez and Agustin Lira, 1966; 2 (Box 2)
  Songs: "Huelga en General" (General Strike) and "El Esquirol" (The Scab). Sung by: Luis Valdez and August Lira. Music by: David Allaniz (Accordion) and Agustin Lira and Danny Valdez (Guitars). Propaganda music disc created through the mutual inspiration of El Teatro Campesino y la Huelga (The Farm Workers Theater and the Strike)
- 5780 RR 70 sides 1-5, 3 (Box 2)
  3M Recording Tape - Reel to Reel Tape
- One Big Union for Two, Doing the Reactionary with Cab Calloway, 1938; 4 (Box 2)
  From the musical Pins and Needles.
- One Big Union for Two, Nobody Makes a Pass at Me with Sonny Schuyler and Millie (Mildred) Weitz, 1938; 5 (Box 2)
  From the musical Pins and Needles. Kay Weber is also associated with this record, although not listed on the label.
- Sing me a Song of Social Significance, Chain Store Daisy with Sonny Schuyler and Ruth Rubenstein, 1938; 6 (Box 2)
- Mene, Mene, Tekel Part Two with Clarence Palmer, 7 (Box 2)
- Sunday in the Park, Doing the Reactionary with Harold Rome, 8 (Box 2)
- Song of the Ads, I Want to be a G-Man with Harold Rome, 9 (Box 2)
- Doing the Reactionary, Sunday in the Park, 10 (Box 2)
  From Pins & Needles by Harold Rome, Hudson-DeLange Orchestra, Broadway showed debuted 1937
- One Big Union for Two, Doing the Reactionary, 11 (Box 2)
  Pins & Needles; Harold J. Rome; Cab Callowy and his Orchestra; Fox Trot, 2 sides
- My Name is Mary Brown, Copy 1, 12 (Box 2)
  Columbia; Musical Narrative by the Northeast Department Before the Golden Jubilee Convention of the ILGWU; 2 sided
- My Name is Mary Brown copy 2, 13 (Box 2)
  Musical Narrative by the Northeast Department before the Golden Jubilee Convention of the ILGWU; Michael Johnson; solos by Gail Manners and Joey Nash
- My Name is Mary Brown, copy 3, 14 (Box 2)
  Musical Narratives by the Northeast Department before the Golden Jubilee Convention for the ILGWU; Michael Johnson; solos by Gail Manners and Joey Nash
- National Anthem of the US, 15 (Box 2)
  The British Broadcasting Corporation (London Transcription Service); BBC Symphony Orchestra with Sir Adrian Bonlt; Composer J. Stafford Smith
- Senora Munoz Marin interviewed by Morris Novick, 16 (Box 2)
  Wife of Governor of Puerto Rico; AF of L Convention in Los Angeles
- New Frontiers 1960, 17 (Box 2)
  Gotham; Version 1 and 2; 10/12/60
- Have a Heart Tart-Hartley, Our Hour copy 1, 18 (Box 2)
  The Puppy Love song (David-Hoffman-Livingston); The Prairie Ramblers
- Have a Heart Taft-Hartley, Our Hour copy 2, 19 (Box 2)
- David Dubinsky, WEVD, 11/1/1942, 20 (Box 2)
  Asch Recording New York NY
- David Dubinsky, WEVD, 11/1/1942, 21 (Box 2)
  Asch Recording, New York, NY; 2 sided
- David Dubinsky at Opening of Seaman's Institute London, 22 (Box 2)
- Tex and Jinx, 4/9/1958 part 1, 23 (Box 2)
  NBC, 2 sided
- Tex and Jinx, 4/9/1958 part 2, 24 (Box 2)
  NBC; 2 sided
- Tex and Jinx, 4/9/1958, 25 (Box 2)
  NBC; TV Time off the air recordings
- Tex and Jinx, 4/14/1958, 26 (Box 2)
- Tex and Jinx, 4/14/1958 part 2, 27 (Box 2)
- We Work- We Sing copy 1, 28 (Box 2)
  Gene and Francesca; Local 91 chorus; New York Joint Board 28th ILGWU Convention; Chicago; May 1953; Side 1 -1. Greetings Isidore Naglar, General Manager, Cloak Joint Board 2. ILGWU Anthem 3. Sing Workers Sing 4. Bread and Roses 5. So Join up Brothers, Sisters 6. We are Building A Strong Union; Side 2- 1. We Shall Not Be Moved 2. Are You Sleeping 3. Keep Us Safe the Union Way 4. March On (Solo Elsie Sussman) 5. Twenty Years Ago 6. Hold the Fort
- The Many Lengths of Fashion 'There's Nothing Like A Dress' May 1953, 29 (Box 2)
  Report to the 28th Convention International Garment Workers' Union by the Joint Board of Cloak, Suit, and Reefer Makers' Unions of Greater New York; 2 sided
- 'There's Nothing Like A Dress' May 1953, 30 (Box 2)
  Report to the 28th Convention ILGWU by the Joint Board of Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Reefer Makers' Unions of Greater New York; Chicago
- We Work- We Sing, May 1953, 31 (Box 2)
  Report to the 28th Convection ILGWU by the Joint Board of Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Reefer Makers' Unions of Greater New York; Chicago
- A Collection of Christmas Songs part 1, 32 (Box 2)
  Christmas In Song Vol. 1 Part1; 1. Christmas Day in the Morning 2. They Come With Blissful Song 3. Baby's Night; Frank Luther and Zora Layman and the Century Quartette; side 2 1. God Rest Ye Merry, Gentlemen 2. Old Christmas 3. Cradle Song of the Virgin
- A Collection of Christmas Songs part 2, 33 (Box 2)
  Christmas in Song Vol. 1. part 3 and 4; 1. Boar Head Carol 2. Old Christmas 3. The Babe of Bethlehem; side 2 1. Good King 2. Far Away; Frank Luther and Zola Layman and the Century Quartette
- A Collection of Christmas Songs part 3, 34 (Box 2)
  Christmas in Song Vol. 1 part 5 and 6 1. The Wassail Song 2. Why, Alas in Lowly Stall 3. The First Nowell; side 2 1. Carol, Carol Christmas 2. When Snow Lies Deep 3. The Sleigh Ride; Frank Luther and Zora Layman and the Century Quartette
- A Collection of Christmas Songs part 4, 35 (Box 2)
  Christmas in Song Vol.1 part 7 1. Hark the Herald Angels Sing 2. O, Come All Ye Faithful, side 2 Calm was the Night 2. 'Twas Clear and Cold 3. Oh Night of Nights! 4. Holy Nigh; Frank Luther and Zola Layman and the Century Quartette
- A Collection of Christmas Songs part 5, 36 (Box 2)
  Christmas in Song Vol. 1. part 9 and 10 1. Joy to the World 2. Born of Maiden Fair 3. Come and Worship, side 2 1. The Holy Family 2. Ave Maria (Schubert); Frank Luther and Zora Layman and the Century Quartette
- The Red Mikado, 37 (Box 2)
  Pins & Needles, Harold J. Rome - Joseph Schrank; Directed by Robert H. Gordon; Vocal Direction by Simon Rady; 2 sided
- Report on the Labor 6/6/50, 38 (Box 2)
  9 to 9:30 PM; side 5 and 7
- Pins and Needles 25th Anniversary Edition of the Hill Musical Revue, 39 (Box 2)
  Barbara Streisand, Rose Marie Jun, Jack Carroll and Harold Rome; 1.Sing Me a Song with Social Significance 2. Doing the Reactionary 3. One Big Union for Two 3. One Big Union for Two 4. It's Better with a Union Man 5. Nobody Makes a pass at me 6. I've got the Nerve to be in Love 7. Not Cricket to Picket 8. Back to Work; side 2 1.
- "Pins and Needles" 5/23/1962, 40 (Box 2)
  25th Anniversary Edition of the Hit Musical Revue Barbara Streisand, Rose Marie Jun, Jack Carroll and Harold Rome; Elise Bretton, Souvenir of the Thirty- First Convention ILGWU; 1. Sing Me A Song With Social Significance 2. Doing The Reactionary 3. One Big Union For Two 4. It's Better With A Union Man 5. Nobody Makes A Pass At Me 6. I've Got The Nerve To Be In Love 7. Not Cricket To Picket 8. Back To Work; side 2 1. Statue Quo 2. When I Grow Up 3. Chain Store Daisy 4. Four Little Angels of Peace 5. Sunday In the Park 6. What Good Love Is 7. Mene, Mene, Tekel
- "Pins and Needles" 5/23/1962, 41 (Box 2)
- "My Name is Mary Brown", 42 (Box 2)
  Northeast Department for the Golden Jubilee Convention of the ILGWU; Michael Johnson; Gail Manners; Jack Nelson; Part 1
- Fashion USA "What's Happening in the World of Fashion", 43 (Box 2)
  1. Shirts for Skirts 2. In praise of pants! 3. Robes 4. No change 5. False Economy 6. The long & short of it 7. Knits 8. Underneath 9. Sleepwear Scene 10. "Suit" Yourself 11. Bathing suits; side 2 1. Spring Forecast 2. New Looks for Spring 3. Do's and Don'ts 4. "In Betweens" 6. Labels on the Level 7. Knits and Sportswear 8. Rain Coats 9. Littlegirl's world 10. Fashion American Style 11. Spring Offering
- "Fashion USA" What's Happening in the World of Fashion, 44 (Box 2)
- "Fashion USA" What's Happening in the World of Fashion, 45 (Box 2)
- "Pins and Needles" 5/23/1962, 46 (Box 2)
  Harold Rome; Jack Carroll; Barbara Streisand; Elise Bretton; Stan Freeman; Elizabeth Lauer; Charles Burr; Rose Marie Jun; Souvenir of the Thirty-First Convention ILGWU; Atlantic City; New Jersey 1. Shirts for Skirts 2. In praise of pants! 3. Robes 4. No change 5. False Economy 6. The long & short of it 7. Knits 8. Underneath 9. Sleepwear Scene 10. "Suit" Yourself 11. Bathing suits; side 2 1. Spring Forecast 2. New Looks for Spring 3. Do's and Don'ts 4. "In Betweens" 6. Labels on the Level 7. Knits and Sportswear 8. Rain Coats 9. Littlegirl's world 10. Fashion American Style 11. Spring Offering
- "Pins and Needles" 5/23/1962, 47 (Box 2)
- "Pins & Needles" 5/23/1962, 48 (Box 2)
- Sidney Hillman Memorial Program 7/30/1947, 1 (Box 3)
  Carnegie Hall; New York City; Dr Stephen S. Wise part 2
- Sidney Hillman Memorial Program 7/30/1947, 2 (Box 3)
  Carnegie Hall; New York City; Dr Stephen S. Wise part 1 & 3
- Sidney Hillman Memorial Program 7/30/1947, 3 (Box 3)
  Carnegie Hall; New York City; Jacob S. Potofsky part 2; Mayor William O'Dwyer Part 2
- Sidney Hillman Memorial Program 7/30/1947, 4 (Box 3)
  Carnegie Hall; New York City; Jacob S. Potofsky part 1; Mayor William O'Dwyer Part 1
- A Progress Report the Biennial Convention, 5 (Box 3)
  Amalgamated Clothing Worker of America part 1 and 2
- A Progress Report to the Biennial Convention, 6 (Box 3)
- A Progress Report to the Biennial Convention, 7 (Box 3)
- Reporte De El Pregreso para la decimonovena Convencion Bienal Distibudio por el Departament de Educacion de la ACWA, 8 (Box 3)
  15 Union Square NYC
- Reporte De El Pregreso para la decimonovena Convencion Bienal Distibudio por el Departament de Educacion de la ACWA, 9 (Box 3)
- Reporte De El Pregreso para la decimonovena Convencion Bienal Distibudio por el Departament de Educacion de la ACWA, 10 (Box 3)
  15 Union Square New York City
- "And Then I Wrote", 11 (Box 3)
  Harold Rome; Pins and Needles; Fanny; Call Me Mister; Wish You Were Here
- Vice Premier Saragat 12/19/1947, 12 (Box 3)
- Vice Premier Saragat 12/19/1947, 13 (Box 3)
- Vice Premier Saragat 12/19/1947, 14 (Box 3)
- John Galo 9/11/38, 15 (Box 3)
  7:30 PM; WHOM Station No. 1 and 3
- John Galo 9/11/38, 16 (Box 3)
  7:30 PM WHOM Stationl No. 2 and 4
- John Galo 9/11/38, 17 (Box 3)
  7:30 PM; WHOM Station No. 5 and 7
- John Galo 9/11/38, 18 (Box 3)
  7:30 PM; WHOM Station; No. 6 and 8
- Dame Ann Loughlin Speech 1950, 19 (Box 3)
  WEVD; Saturday
- Untitled, 20 (Box 3)
  RR78 part 1
- Untitled, 21 (Box 3)
  RR78 part 2
- Speech by Luigi Antonini 7/13/1946, 22 (Box 3)
  Buenos Aires Part 3
- TV Time Off-The-Air Recordings, 23 (Box 3)
  White Plains, New York; John F Kennedy; Sen.. Clinton P. Anderson; David Dubinsky; Mayor Robert F. Wagner
- Speech by Luigi Antonini 7/13/1946, 24 (Box 3)
  Buenos Aires, part 3
- Luigi Antonini 9/27/1946, 25 (Box 3)
  Part 3
- National Emblem March & Labor's Service to Freedom, 26 (Box 3)
  Hon. Samuel Gumpers